<speech>
	<Book>
		<dialogue>
			"Hello, just woke up? You're in jail for life...
			You probably don't remember why but that doesn't matter right now.
			Why don't you have a little look around? Maybe you'll get some hints as to why.
			Enclosed in this book is the key to your cell, tread carefully..."
			
			You obtained the key to your cell.
			<objective>Leave your cell</objective>
		</dialogue>
	</Book>

	<MobMember>
		<dialogue currState="1">
			"Psst. Hey, stupid, I'm in with some powerful people round here; You still owe us more favours.
			In return for your continued loyalty, we will protect you.
			Deliver this package to Trippie Maroon on the top floor."
			<choice>Yes
				<dialogue>
					"Cheers buddy"
				
					You obtained a small package
				</dialogue>
				<objective>Deliver Package</objective>
				<state>1.1</state>
			</choice>
			<choice>No
				<dialogue>"I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that and ask you again..."
				<state>1</state>
				</dialogue>
			</choice>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Don't ask any questions you don't wanna know the answer to."
		</dialogue>
	</MobMember>
	
	<Rainbow>
		<dialogue currState="1.4">
			You call Rainbow over and distract him as you quickly sneak a laxative into his cup of water.
				<state>1.5</state>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.5">
			Rainbow's stomach starts making some noises.
			
			Oh Jesus, that lady must have cooked up some real bad food!
			
			He runs off in an awkward pose back to his cell.
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.6">
			He gives you a grimace. His stomach makes some more noises.
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Can't believe I went 11/11 and now I'm here."
		</dialogue>
	</Rainbow>
	
	<TheGambler>
		<dialogue>
			"You get some cards and a dice and I'm down to gamble with you"
		</dialogue>
	</TheGambler>
	
	<Prisoner>
		<dialogue>
			"I've been arrested 7 times, I know that sounds like quite a lot but three
			of those times were for vandalism."
		</dialogue>
	</Prisoner>
	
	<IllPrisoner>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner looked incredibly pale and frightened.
		</dialogue>
	</IllPrisoner>

	<TrippieMaroon>
		<dialogue currState="1">
			"What you staring at?"
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.1">
			"Yo, WrayTay sent you? Pass that here."
			
			Trippie Maroon opens the package
			
			"Yes! I needed this... 
			Hey, if you get bored, talk to me again yeah."
			<state> 1.2</state>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.2">
			"You got bored quick, there is this guy with rainbow hair in this block I hate
			He has been messing with me for weeks now, I need you to take care of him.
			The dinner lady has the worst smoking habit this side on the ocean and you can 
			trade her cigarettes for pretty much anything. Take these and buy me some laxatives."
			
			Trippie hands you 5 cigarettes
			<state> 1.3</state>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.3">
			"Get going!"
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.5">
			"Ha! I saw the rainbow haired prick waddling to his cell. Cheers pal, I just might have more use for you..."
				<state>1.6</state>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"I might have some more work for you soon. I'll be in touch."
		</dialogue>
	</TrippieMaroon>
	
	<AggressivePrisoner>
		<dialogue currState="1.3">
			"Just cause Trippie's got you as his errand boy ain't mean nothin' to me if you get in my way again"
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Who you staring at boy?"
		</dialogue>
	</AggressivePrisoner>
	
	<PlacementApplication>
		<dialogue>
			"I strike fear into the hearts of everyone who knows my name...
			My name is Placement Application"
			
			You felt a shudder down your spine for some reason
		</dialogue>
	</PlacementApplication>
	
	<BadManners>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner spits at you
		</dialogue>
	</BadManners>
	
	<Spades>
		<dialogue>
			"Listen, you're gonna need to earn something valuable to trade if you wanna get by here.
			Lucky for you, I've got a proposition for you, you bring me 2 packets of ramen,
			then I'll give you my lucky dice and deck."
		</dialogue>
	</Spades>
	
	<Loony>
		<dialogue>
			"Have you heard the rumour that you can hear screams in the basement at midnight?"
			
			You found this disturbing
		</dialogue>
	</Loony>
	
	<ShakyPrisoner>
		<dialogue currState="1.2">
			"Listen man, I saw you doing stuff with them, leave me alone."
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.3">
			"Listen man, I saw you doing stuff with them, leave me alone."
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Leave me be man, I don't want any problems today"
		</dialogue>
	</ShakyPrisoner>
	
	<DinnerLady>
		<dialogue currState="1.3">
			"You'd think I wouldn't have my sense of smell anymore, but I know tobacco anywhere. 
			Trippie sent you? He ordered this the other day, slide what you got under the tray."
			
			You passed her the 5 cigarettes, in return you get some laxatives.
				<state>1.4</state>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1.4">
			"You know what those are right? Don't even try one else you won't be out of your cell for while."
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Today we are serving our special of sardines and sadness...
			
			Unless you got something for me?"
		</dialogue>
	</DinnerLady>
	
	<DisgustedPrisoner>
		<dialogue>
			"Every day this food gets worse."
		</dialogue>
	</DisgustedPrisoner>
	
	<Biggie>
		<dialogue>
			"I can't believe I'm eating this crap"
		</dialogue>
	</Biggie>
	
	<AnotherMobMember>
		<dialogue>
			"I miss having fresh air and the peep show"
		</dialogue>
	</AnotherMobMember>
	
	<Ray>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner stares at you.
		</dialogue>
	</Ray>
	
	<Joe>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner gives you a nod.
		</dialogue>
	</Joe>
	
	<Tweak>
		<dialogue>
			As you approach, he twitches and scurries about, seemingly uncontrollably muttering something 
			about an MVP and coffee...
			
			You figure it's best you left him alone for now.
		</dialogue>
	</Tweak>
	
	<Tim>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner stares at you.
		</dialogue>
	</Tim>
	
	<Moon>
		<dialogue>
			The prisoner gives you a nod.
		</dialogue>
	</Moon>
	
	<Warden>
		<dialogue currState="1h">
			"So have you done it?"
			<choice>yes
				<dialogue>
					"Thanks very much, I knew something was going on. I have many eyes and ears and you're one of them now."
				</dialogue>
			</choice>
			<choice>no
				<dialogue>
					"Alright then. Just know, I reward people who provide me information."
				</dialogue>
			</choice>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue currState="1">
			Would you like to hand in the mission?
			<choice>no
				<dialogue>
					The warden stares at you expectantly
				</dialogue>
			</choice>
			<choice>yes
				<dialogue>
					"Oh you've done the thing?"
				</dialogue>
				<state>1h</state>
			</choice>
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Get out of here unless you want people to know you're a snitch"
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"Thanks for the info. The culprit will be... dealt with."
		</dialogue>
		<dialogue>
			"I won't push you for it, but I hope you'll strongly reconsider next time... Now get out!"
		</dialogue>
	</Warden>
</speech>