<!-- daytime !-->
<speech>
  <mobBoss>
    <dialogue currstate="2">
      "Finally I've been waiting for you.

      I need your skills to escape."
      <choice>What do you need me to do?
        <dialogue>
          "Firstly we need to be able to move freely around here.
          there's a guy around here called the Gambler,
          he owes me a favour so he'll teach you how to pick the locks in here."
        </dialogue>
        <state>2.1</state>
      </choice>
      <choice>Why me?
        <dialogue>
          "Just remember who you work for. If you ever forget, you'll see just how hard life can be."
          now find the Gambler, he'll teach you what you need to know."
        </dialogue>
        <state>2.1</state>
      </choice>
    </mobBoss>

    <!-- TO BE DONE ALL IN NIGHT TIME, MISSION 1 !-->
    <!-- Link up with gambler, do what you need to do for him and get him to teach you on how to pick locks !-->
    <TheGambler>
      <dialogue currstate="2.1">
        "I wonder why someone like you would be helping that evil man escape.
        I'm not sure if I can trust you kid. Rainbow's a good judge of character,
        If he vouches for you, then we'll talk.
        <state>2.2</state>
        <objective>Find Rainbow</objective>
      </dialogue>

      <dialogue currstate="2.5">
        "I got word from Rainbow, he says you're alrght kid.
        dunno how, but that boys always been good at picking the bad apples out the bunch.

        I guess I could teach you a thing or two about picking locks"
        <choice>Teach me
          <puzzle>2.6</puzzle>
          <objective>Speak to the Gambler</objective>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
      <!--puzzle take you to 2.6-->
      <dialogue currstate="2.6">
        You're a fast learner, you picked that up quick.
        Though you won't be breaking into any high tech vaults with this,
        but getting around these old prison doors should be a breeze now."
        <choice>Why dont you like the boss?
          <dialogue>
            "You really don't remember?
            Damn... they must have done a number on you,
            It's a lot to explain. Mostly rumors, but before you do anything drastic come back and we'll talk"
          </dialogue>
          <state>3</state> <!--end of chapter 2-->
          <objective>Speak to the Gambler again</objective>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
    </TheGambler>

    <Rainbow>
      <!-- Minigame with rainbow which allows player to do minigames in free time !-->
      <!-- Nothing to do with main mission !-->
      <dialogue currState="2.2">
        "I'll tell you what, I'll put in a good word to gambler if you help me with something."
        I heard you were good at computers on the outside?

        Trippie likes to send his girls emails on the lirbrary computers,
        need you to hack into Trippie's account and send his girlfriend a little message for me."
        <choice>Whats the message?
          <dialogue>
            "Tell her that he's been seeing someone else on the inside.
            And that things are over... Yeah that should teach him not to mess with me again.

            You help me, I'll help you."
          </dialogue>
          <state>2.3</state>
          <objective>Hack Trippie</objective>
          <!-- hacking puzzle takes you to state 2.4-->
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
      <dialogue currState="2.3">
        "You done that thing for me yet?"
        <choice>I don't know how to hack
          <dialogue>
            "I heard you were good with these things though... Hm."

            Trippie pulls out a phone and hands it to you.

            "Here, try with this, I'm sure it'll come back to you."
          </dialogue>
          <puzzle>2.3</puzzle>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
      <dialogue currState="2.4">
        You managed to do it? I knew you could.

        I can't wait to see that son of a bitch moping around for the next
        2 weeks.

        Anyway, I said I'll put in a good word, you've done enough for me.
        <state>2.5</state>
        <objective>Speak to the Gambler</objective>
      </dialogue>
    </Rainbow>

    <Computer>
      <dialogue currState="2.3">
        You log onto the computer.
        Everything seems so familiar to you, but you don't know why.

        Let's do the job.
        <choice>Hack
          <puzzle>2.3.1</puzzle>
          <objective>Hack Trippie[1/3]</objective>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
      <dialogue currState="2.3.1">
        You've made it into Trippie's emails. You rummage around and find
        the site he uses for these messages.
        <choice>Keep Going
          <puzzle>2.3.2</puzzle>
          <objective>Hack Trippie[2/3]</objective>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
      <dialogue currState="2.3.2">
        You've pwned both the email and his site account now.
        Time to send the final message.
        <!--Have a choice here to ruin Trippie or not?-->
        <choice>Send Heartless Message
          <dialogue>
            You craft a cold and cruel message to break up with this poor girl.

            You feel a little guilty, but maybe she shouldn't be with Trippie anyway.
            Your inner monologue makes you feel a bit better about yourself.
          </dialogue>
          <state>2.4</state>
          <objective>Speak to Rainbow</objective>
        </choice>
        <choice>Let her down gently
          <dialogue>
            You put some effort into trying to be as gentle as possible with this.

            You suddenly realise that you're really invested in this fictional breakup
            and that you've also wrote 5 pages. Maybe it's time to click send.
          </dialogue>
          <state>2.4</state>
          <objective>Speak to Rainbow</objective>
        </choice>
      </dialogue>
    </Computer>

    <!--ADD MISC NPC DIALOGUE HERE-->

  </speech>
